I knew a guy once
Chlápka já jsem jednou znal
Onar was his name
Onar on se jmenoval
Old, he was - and dangerous,
Starý byl – a hrozivý
always had a worried face
ve tváři vždy obavy
He found some weed in the clothing chest
V truhle s hadry našel trávu
After he had smoked it, he started dancing with the villagers
Šluknul si a tančil v davu
In swampweed there is enchanted power,
Moc zakletou v trávě z bažin
you won't find this in books, so I welcome the customer
nevyčteš z knih – klient, prosím
If you want to smoke a bit of swampweed
Chceš-li si dát trochu trávy
I introduce you to Cipher, the best dealer
dealer Cipher tě vybaví
We like to smoke, because it give us power
Tráva to je láska, sílu nám všem dodá
I want one puff, I'm not asking for much more!
Dej mi jenom práska, víc by byla škoda!
Do you know what's green, small and grows on the swamp?
Zelené a malé, roste to v bažinách?
It's swampweed, that's its pretty name
To je tráva z bažin, tak zve se bylina
We like to smoke, because it gives us power
Tráva to je láska, sílu nám všem dodá
I want one puff, I'm not asking for much more!
Dej mi jenom práska, víc by byla škoda!
Do you know what's green, small and grows on the swamp?
Zelené a malé, roste to v bažinách?
It's swampweed, that's its pretty name
To je tráva z bažin, tak zve se bylina
You probably know Rosi,
Jistě znáte Rosi,
It's Sekob's wife
Je Sekobovou ženou
She constantly complains that her leg hurts a lot
Pořád stěžuje si s nohou namoženou
She started smoking weed,
Začla hulit trávu,
this is the fourth pack already
a po čtyřech krábách
She got so stoned, she started doing flips off the roof
zhulená jak papuč salta ze střech dává
In swampweed, there is enchanted power,
Moc zakletou v trávě z bažin
you won't find this in books, so I welcome the customer
nevyčte z knih – klient, prosím
If you want to smoke a bit of swampweed,
Chceš-li si dát trochu trávy,
I introduce you to Cipher, the best dealer
dealer Cipher tě vybaví
We like to smoke, because it gives us power
Tráva to je láska, sílu nám všem dodá
I want one puff, I'm not asking for much more!
Dej mi jenom práska, víc by byla škoda!
Do you know what's small, green and grows on the swamp?
Zelené a malé, roste to v bažinách?
It's swampweed, that's its pretty name
To je tráva z bažin, tak zve se bylina
We like to smoke, because it gives us power
Tráva to je láska, sílu nám všem dodá
I want one puff, I'm not asking for much more!
Dej mi jenom práska, víc by byla škoda!
Do you know what's green, small and grows on the swamp?
Zelené a malé, roste to v bažinách?
It's swampweed, that's its pretty name
To je tráva z bažin, tak zve se bylina
¯\_(ツ)_/¯
¯\_(ツ)_/¯
Special thanks to Ortega, for bringing the idea and model for the "armor"
Velké díky patří Ortegovi za nápad a model "zbroje"
Aswell as Haze for making a great thumbnail
a Hazeovi za skvělý náhledový obrázek
You'll find links to their fanpages in the description, I recommend visiting  ;)
Odkazy na jejich fanstránky najdete v popisu, doporučuji navštívit ;)
If you want to download the remix or the instrumental alone, I invite you to my fanpage
Jestli si chceš stáhnout remix nebo instrumentál, navštiv moji fanstránku
[ENG sub by Gat1Day]
[Český překlad: Zero]